The best interest savings account in the
world for me has been social media.
Whenever I've had a spare 10K,
I put it into camera, mic,
studio, all of these things.
Even my last book deal I've signed,
I got my
advance. They paid me way too much.
I've given it half away already to my
favorite author to help me write it.
Whenever I get money, I think,
"How can I use this to make more money?"
I'm putting
it into the social media interest savings
account and writing a book because by
doing that book, I get more content,
I get more things to talk about,
more things
to... Anyway, it comes back full circle.
If I just put that money
and put it into a fucking ETF, cool.
It might compound over a few years
and build generational wealth.
Or I'll hire a fucking weapon that's going
to make me write a book that's 10 times
better,
and I'll get the money back in a year
or two